Finding Aid for Alvin M. Bentley Papers 1935-1969
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Senatorial Campaign 1960
  - Miscellaneous campaign files
    - Campaign Workers by County
      - Mackinac-Macomb (Box 41)
      - Manistee-Midland (Box 41)
      - Missaukee-Newaygo (Box 41)
      - Oakland (Box 41)
      - Oakland July 29, 1960 meeting (Box 41)
      - Oceana-Ottawa (Box 41)
      - Presque Isle-Saginaw (Box 41)
      - Sanilac-Shiawassee (Box 42)
      - St. Clair-Washtenaw (Box 42)
      - Wayne-Wexford (Box 42)
    - County list of Bentley for Senate committee members and supporters (Box 42)
    - Wayne County congressional districts-officers and board members (Box 42)
    - Political contacts, thirteenth through eighteenth congressional districts (Box 42)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Bentley for Senate committee (Box 42)
    - Correspondence related to campaign
      - January-November 1960, 13 folders (Box 42)
    - Speeches, campaign, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Speeches-background materials (Box 42)
    - Progress Reports of Bentley for Senate Committee (Box 42)
    - Press Releases
      - April-October, 10 folders (Box 42)
      - Unreleased (Box 42)
    - Media contacts-lists of Michigan newspapers and television & radio stations (Box 42)
    - Itineraries
      - April-May (Box 42)
      - June (invitations) (Box 42)
      - June (Box 42)
      - July (invitations) (Box 42)
      - July (Box 42)
      - August (Box 42)
      - September, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - October, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Correspondence (Box 43)
      - Mrs. Bentley (October) (Box 43)
    - Campaign Appearances (Box 43)
    - Petitions for Senate Race, include materials concerning:
      - Filing (Box 43)
      - County-by-county status (Box 43)
      - Correspondence (outgoing) (Box 43)
      - Correspondence (incoming) (Box 43)
      - List of persons circulating petitions (Box 43)
      - 1960 Wayne county (one envelope) (Box 43)
    - Election Polls (Box 43)
    - Election Analysis-Michigan Campaigns 1950-1958 (Box 43)
    - Post-primary election analyses (Box 43)
    - Unofficial tally of votes November 8, 1960 McNamara-Bentley, Swainson-Bagwell, Kennedy-Nixon, Hamtramck vote (Box 43)
    - Official Canvass of votes and post-election evaluations (Box 43)
    - Election returns, Genesee & Lapeer counties (Box 43)
    - Post election correspondence, in state, 4 folders (Box 43)
    - Post election correspondence, out state (Box 43)
    - Clippings
      - Bagwell, Paul (Box 43)
      - Kennedy, John (Box 43)
      - McNamara, Patrick (Box 43)
      - Nixon, Richard (Box 43)
      - Romney, George (Box 43)
      - Staebler, Neil (Box 43)
      - Summerfield, Arthur (Box 43)
      - Vandenberg, Arthur (Box 43)
      - Announcement (Box 43)
      - Anti-Catholic campaign (Box 43)
      - Bentley-Leonard-McNamara (Box 43)
      - Bentley, campaign expenses (Box 43)
      - Bentley, campaign positions (Box 43)
      - Bentley, personal (Box 43)
      - Bentley, endorsements (Box 43)
      - Bentley, speaking engagements (Box 43)
      - Democrats (Box 43)
      - Greeks (Box 43)
      - Labor (Box 43)
      - McCarthy, Joseph & Bentley (Box 43)
      - Michigan politics (Box 43)
      - National Republican Convention (Box 43)
      - Negroes (Box 43)
      - Poles (Box 43)
      - Political advertising (Box 43)
      - Shiawassee (Owosso) candidates (Box 43)
      - general (Box 43)
- Constitutional Convention 1961-1963
  Constitutional Convention (7 linear ft.; 1961-1963) consists of correspondence and papers created and collected while Bentley served as a delegate to the convention.
  - Correspondence
    - January-December 1961, 26 folders (Box 44)
    - January-August 1962, 19 folders (Box 44)
    - November 13, 1961-May 11, 1962 (outgoing), 1 volumes (Box 44)
    - 1963 (Box 45)
    - re education issues discussed at the Constitutional Convention, A-Z (Box 45)
  - Committee Files
    - Committee on Administration (Box 45)
    - Committee on Education, 4 folders (Box 45)
    - Committee on Emerging Problems (Box 45)
    - Committee on Executive Branch, 6 folders (Box 45)
    - Committee on Finance & Taxation, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Committee on Judicial Branch (Box 45)
    - Committee on Legislative Organization (Box 45)
    - Committee on Legislative Organization (cont.) (Box 46)
    - Committee on Legislative Powers (Box 46)
    - Committee on Local Government, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Committee on Miscellaneous Provision and Schedules (Box 46)
    - Committee on Public Information (Box 46)
    - Committee on Rights, Suffrage & Elections (Box 46)
    - Committee on Rules & Regulations, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Committee on Style & Drafting (Box 46)
  - Various
    - Con-Con Issues (Box 46)
      - Courts (Box 46)
      - Highways (Box 46)
      - Taxation (Box 46)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 46)
    - Papers on Con-Con related topics, 4 folders (Box 46)
    - Papers concerning George Romney's role in Con-Con (Box 46)
    - Con-Con candidates and delegates-profiles (Box 46)
    - Papers related to Bentley's Con-Con campaign & election, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Bentley's Con-Con speeches & itinerary (Box 46)
    - Citizen's Research Council of Michigan-Council Comments December 1961-May 1962 (Box 46)
    - Citizen's Research Council of Michigan-Miscellanea (Box 46)
    - Citizen's Research Council of Michigan-Publications on Con-Con (Box 46)
    - Coordinating Committee for Con-Con (Box 46)
    - Gongwer (Lansing, Mich.) News Service, Inc. Reports October 1961 (Box 46)
    - League of Women Voters (Michigan) Press Releases on Con-Con October 1961-January 1962, January-March 1963 (Box 46)
    - Michigan Con-Con Weekly Reports December 1961-March 1963 (Box 47)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents-Bulletins 1962 (Box 47)
    - Michigan Education Association-Legislative Bulletins (Box 47)
    - Michigan Manufacturers Association-Reports (Box 47)
    - Private files pulled from Con-Con (Box 47)
    - Public Information Committee (Con-Con) Weekly Delegates Reports November 1961-April 1962 (Box 47)
    - Public Information Committee (Con-Con)--Delegates' Column December 1961-May 1962 (Box 47)
    - Reading lists of materials on constitutional revision (Box 47)
    - Republican Con-Con Educational committee (Box 47)
    - Select Committee to Place Constitution on Public Ballot (Box 47)
    - Clippings
      - Administration (Box 47)
      - Declaration of Rights, Suffrage & Election (Box 47)
      - Education, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Executive Branch, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Finance & Taxation, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - General Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Judicial Branch, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Legislative Organization, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Legislative Powers (Box 47)
      - Local Government (Box 47)
      - Miscellaneous provisions & Schedules, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Public Information (Box 47)
      - Rules & Resolutions, 2 folders (Box 47)
      - Style & Drafting (Box 47)
    - Notebooks and published materials on Con-Con & related topics
      (also includes additional newspaper clippings)
      - Notebooks and published materials on Con-Con & related topics (Box 48)
      - Notebooks and published materials on Con-Con & related topics (Box 49)
        (continued)
      - Notebooks and published materials on Con-Con & related topics (Box 50)
- Congressional Campaign 1962
  Congressional Campaign (6 linear ft.; 1962) documents Bentley's campaign in the special congressman-at-large election of 1962. The series includes correspondence, press releases, staff and county coordinator files, speeches, topical files on the running of the campaign, and issues files.
  - Correspondence
    - May-November 1962, 11 folders (Box 51)
    - 1962-1963 with George Romney concerning gubernatorial appointments (Box 51)
    - Thank-you letters to campaign help, A-Z (Box 51)
  - Press Releases
    - May-November 1962, 11 folders (Box 51)
  - Campaign Staff: correspondence, memoranda & assorted materials
    - Campaign personnel-general (Box 51)
    - Campaign personnel-applications (Box 51)
    - Campaign Strategy Information (Box 51)
    - Campaign daily reports (Box 52)
    - Campaign headquarters (Detroit) (Box 52)
    - Campaign general staff (Box 52)
    - Campaign staff memoranda, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Charles Anspach (Box 52)
    - Alvin Bentley (Box 52)
    - Mike Carl (Box 52)
    - Norman DesJardin (Box 52)
    - Dottie Farber (Box 52)
    - Al Forbes (Box 52)
    - Mitz Gentile (Box 52)
    - Jean Seeley Greene (Box 52)
    - Rae Hooker (Box 52)
    - Signe Karlstron (Box 52)
    - Pete McPherson (Box 52)
    - D.J. Mitchell, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Jerry Petit (Box 52)
    - Shirley Quinn (Box 52)
    - William Reid, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Grant Renier (Box 52)
    - Phygenar Stephens (Box 52)
    - Leigh Thomas (Box 52)
    - Volunteers for Bentley (Box 52)
    - Ed Walsh (Box 52)
    - Walter Wasacz (Box 52)
    - Allen Weatherwax (Box 52)
    - Philip Weiss, 4 folders (Box 52)
    - Bernice White (Box 52)
    - Women's Committee for Bentley, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Young Republicans (Box 52)
  - Bentley for Congress County Coordinators
    - General information, 2 folders (Box 52)
    - Alcona-Alger (Box 52)
    - Allegan-Arenac (Box 52)
    - Baraga-Bay (Box 53)
    - Benzie-Branch (Box 53)
    - Calhoun-Cass (Box 53)
    - Charlevoix-Chippewaw (Box 53)
    - Clare-Emmet (Box 53)
    - Genesee-Grand Traverse (Box 53)
    - Gratiot-Gogebic (Box 53)
    - Hillsdale-Huron (Box 53)
    - Ingham (Box 53)
    - Ionia-Isabella (Box 53)
    - Jackson-Kalkaska (Box 53)
    - Kent-Keweenaw (Box 53)
    - Lake-Luce (Box 53)
    - Machinac-Mason (Box 53)
    - Mecosta-Missaukee (Box 53)
    - Monroe-Montorency (Box 53)
    - Muskegon-Newaygo (Box 53)
    - Oakland-Ottawa (Box 53)
    - Presque Isle-Saginaw (Box 53)
    - St. Clair-Shiawassee (Box 53)
    - Tuscola-Wexford (Box 53)
  - Campaign Appearances/Itineraries and Speeches
    - Correspondence January-November 1962, 10 folders (Box 53)
    - Correspondence on campaign appearances
      - January-August 1962, 6 folders (Box 53)
      - September 1-19, 1962 (Box 53)
      - September 20-30, 1962 (Box 53)
      - October 1-5, 1962 (Box 53)
      - October 6-10, 1962 (Box 54)
      - October 11-12, 1962 (Box 54)
      - October 13-16, 1962 (Box 54)
      - October 17-21, 1962 (Box 54)
      - October 22-24, 1962 (Box 54)
      - October 25-28, 1962 (Box 54)
      - October 29-31, 1962 (Box 54)
      - November 1962 (Box 54)
    - Regrets on campaign appearances January-November 1962, 4 folders (Box 54)
    - Speeches, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Speech reference and background materials-general topics, 5 folders (Box 54)
    - Speech reference and background materials-medicare, 5 folders (Box 54)
    - Speech reference and background materials-medicare (cont.), 2 folders (Box 55)
  - General campaign materials
    - Advertising (radio-television) (Box 55)
    - Bumper stickers & cards (Box 55)
    - Fair appearances (Box 55)
    - Finance Luncheons (Box 55)
    - Form letters (Box 55)
    - Michigan Newspapers (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 55)
    - Other candidates (Box 55)
    - Petitions
      - list of circulators, 2 folders (Box 55)
      - postage, receipts, etc. (Box 55)
      - statistics, 2 folders (Box 55)
      - special thank-you letters (Box 55)
    - Republican State Central Committee, 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Romney for Governor campaign-general information, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Romney for Governor campaign-correspondence (Box 55)
    - Romney for Governor campaign-schedules (Box 55)
    - Staebler campaign (Box 55)
    - Neil Staebler: Profile of the boss (Box 55)
    - Supplies, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Votemaker questionnaires
      - Circulators (Box 56)
      - Correspondence (Box 56)
      - Distribution (Box 56)
      - Returns (Box 56)
      - Worksheet reports (Box 56)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Vote Returns (Box 56)
      - Primary Election (Box 56)
      - Final Election, 3 folders (Box 56)
    - Michigan Republican State Convention Press book (Box 56)
    - Booklets on campaign issues
      - Minimum wage (Box 56)
      - Tax Reform (Box 56)
      - Economy (Box 56)
      - Desired Job Level (Box 56)
      - Federal Aid to Education (Box 56)
    - A Fact Book for Republican Campaigners 1962 (Box 56)
    - How to Win Votes & Influence People (Box 56)
    - Congressional Quarterly Election Report (1962) (Box 56)
    - Michigan State Chamber of Commerce-A Roster of Nominees (Box 56)
    - Notebook of clippings on Bentley vs. Staebler (Box 56)
    - Two Notebooks of clippings on other candidates (Box 56)
    - Clippings-general, 2 folders (Box 56)
    - Scrapbook (unbound)-Women Volunteers for Bentley (Signe Karlstrom) (Box 56)
- Citizens Committee on Higher Education 1963-1965
  Citizens Committee on Higher Education (8 linear ft.; 1963-1965) includes meeting files, working files of the committee and its subcommittees, reference and background information, and clippings on educational matters.
  - Correspondence
    - Executive Committee (Box 57)
    - Committee, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Study Committee I,II,IV, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Study Committee III, 4 folders (Box 57)
    - General, 8 folders (Box 57)
    - with George Romney (Box 57)
  - Background file, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Reports of meetings (executive committee and full committee) (Box 57)
  - Governor's Education Budget, 3 folders (Box 57)
  - Regional meeting
    - Dearborn May 5, 1965 and Detroit, May 11, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Kalamazoo May 19, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Flint May 20, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Grand Rapids May 24, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Traverse City May 26, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Marquette, June 1, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Ann Arbor December 4, 1965 (Box 57)
    - Memoranda (Box 57)
  - Correspondence, Citizens Research Council of Michigan (Box 57)
  - Reference materials, Citizens Research Council of Michigan, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Bentley speeches, 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Bentley appearances and invitations (Box 58)
  - Final Committee report (Box 58)
  - Reference materials
    - General (Box 58)
    - Subcommittee 1-A (Box 58)
    - Subcommittee 1-B (Box 58)
    - Subcommittee 1-C (Box 58)
    - Subcommittee II, 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Subcommittee III, 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Subcommittee IV (Box 58)
  - Study Committee on Sault Ste. Marie branch of Michigan Technological College:
    - Committee correspondence (Box 58)
    - General (Box 58)
    - Minutes of Meetings (Box 58)
    - Final Report (Box 58)
    - Reference materials, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - Clippings (Box 58)
    - Printed materials (Box 58)
  - Reference and Background materials for Higher Education Comm.
    - Staff Consultants (Kenneth Morse, Harold Taylor & Harold Smith) files, 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Universities and Colleges, 4 folders (Box 59)
    - Community Colleges (Box 59)
    - Private Colleges (Box 59)
    - General information, 4 folders (Box 59)
    - Michigan Association of Colleges and Universities (Box 59)
    - Michigan Council of Community College Administrators (Box 59)
    - Michigan Council on Economic Education, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council (Box 59)
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 59)
    - Saginaw Valley, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Flint, 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Federal Commission on Higher Education (Box 60)
    - Printed materials on state, private & public colleges (Box 60)
  - Film strip and program on Higher Education Committee
  - Clippings on Educational Matters (Box 61)
    - Administration & Faculty
      - College Administration (Box 61)
      - Faculty (Box 61)
      - Teachers-Organization and Standards including licensing, 5 folders (Box 61)
      - Teachers-Tax Deduction (Box 61)
    - Advisory Groups
      - Board of Control, 3 folders (Box 61)
      - Blue Ribbon Committee, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Council of Michigan College Presidents (Box 61)
      - State Board of Education, 3 folders (Box 61)
      - Department of Education (Box 61)
      - School Boards (Box 61)
    - Colleges and Universities-General
      - College Students-General, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Community Colleges, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Federal Scholarships-Colleges & Universities (Box 61)
      - Financing Education-Colleges & Universities, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Public & Private Colleges (Box 61)
      - Research, 3 folders (Box 61)
      - Branches (Box 61)
    - Education-General
      - Curricula (Box 61)
      - Curricula & Standards (Box 61)
      - Education Costs, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Education for Handicapped (Box 61)
      - Education-miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 61)
      - Enrollments, 2 folders (Box 61)
      - Enrollments, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Tuition (Box 62)
    - Elementary-Secondary-General
      - Elementary-Secondary Education, 3 folders (Box 62)
      - Elementary-Secondary Private and Parochial Schools, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Elementary-Secondary School Standards & Curriculum, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - High-School Dropouts, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Employment
      - Adult Education (Box 62)
      - Employment for College Graduates (Box 62)
      - Employment for High School Graduates (Box 62)
      - Employment for Junior College Graduates (Box 62)
      - Juvenile Delinquency, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Nursing (Box 62)
      - Professional Education (Box 62)
      - Technical-Vocational Education, 4 folders (Box 62)
      - Shiawassee Vocational Program (Box 62)
    - Federal
      - Education Aid for Children of Veterans (Box 62)
      - Federal Aid for Buildings, 3 folders (Box 62)
      - Federal Aid to Higher Education (Box 62)
      - Federal Aid to Students (Box 62)
      - Federal Legislation-Education, 8 folders (Box 62)
    - Private and Parochial-General
      - Aid to Private Colleges (Scholarships) (Box 62)
      - Private and Parochial Colleges (Box 62)
    - Public Schools
      - Detroit Public Schools, 5 folders (Box 62)
      - Prayer in Public Schools, 3 folders (Box 62)
      - Public Schools Integration, 2 folders (Box 62)
      - Public Schools-Local Financing, 2 folders (Box 62)
    - State
      - Accounting (Box 62)
      - Con-Con Education Article (Box 62)
      - School Districts Organization (Box 62)
      - State Aid for Building (Box 62)
      - State Aid to Community Colleges (Box 63)
      - State Aid to Four Year Colleges, 2 folders (Box 63)
      - State Aid to Higher Education-General (Box 63)
      - State Scholarships (Box 63)
      - State Aid to School Districts, 3 folders (Box 63)
      - Compulsory Attendance (Box 63)
      - School buses (Box 63)
      - Loans to College Students (Box 63)
    - Colleges
      - Adrian (Box 63)
      - Albion (Box 63)
      - Alma (Box 63)
      - Alpena Community College (Box 63)
      - Cadillac (Box 63)
      - Clare-Gladwin (Box 63)
      - Calvin College (Box 63)
      - Cass County Community College (Box 63)
      - Central Michigan University, 2 folders (Box 63)
      - Delta College (Box 63)
      - Detroit Institute of Technology (Box 63)
      - Downriver Community College (Box 63)
      - Duns Scotas (Box 63)
      - Eastern Michigan University (Box 63)
      - Ferris State College (Box 63)
      - Flint-U-M Branch, 3 folders (Box 63)
      - Flint-U-M Brand, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - Flint Junior College (Box 64)
      - General Motors Institute (Box 64)
      - Grand Valley College (Box 64)
      - Henry Ford Community College (Box 64)
      - Hillsdale College (Box 64)
      - Hope College (Box 64)
      - Highland Park Community College (Box 64)
      - Kalamazoo College (Box 64)
      - Kellogg Community College (Box 64)
      - Lansing Community College, 2 folders (Box 64)
      - Lake Michigan Community College (Box 64)
      - Lawrence Institute of Technology (Box 64)
      - Livingston Community College (Box 64)
      - Ludington Community College (Box 64)
      - Mackinaw College (Box 64)
      - Macomb College (Box 64)
      - Marygrove College (Box 64)
      - Mercy College (Box 64)
      - Michigan Christian College (Box 64)
      - Michigan College of Osteopathic Medicine (Box 64)
      - Michigan State University, 7 folders (Box 64)
      - Michigan Technological University (Box 64)
      - Monroe County Community College (Box 64)
      - Montcalm County Community College (Box 64)
      - Muskegon County Community College (Box 64)
      - Northern Michigan University (Box 64)
      - Northwood Institute (Box 64)
      - North Central Michigan College (Box 64)
      - Northwestern Michigan College (Box 64)
      - Oakland University (Box 64)
      - Olivet College (Box 64)
      - Owosso Community College (Box 64)
      - Saginaw Valley Community College (Box 64)
      - Schoolcraft Community College (Box 64)
      - Siena Heights College (Box 64)
      - Southwestern Michigan College (Box 64)
      - Suomi College (Box 64)
      - St. Joseph Community College (Box 64)
      - Tri-County Community College (Box 64)
      - University of Detroit (Box 64)
      - University of Michigan, 5 folders (Box 64)
      - Washtenaw Community College (Box 64)
      - Western Michigan University (Box 64)
      - Wayne State University, 4 folders (Box 64)
- State Board of Education Campaign 1964
  State Board of Education Campaign (0.5 linear ft.; 1964) consists of correspondence, speeches, campaign materials, and background information accumulated during Bentley's campaign for this state office.
  - Correspondence September-December 1964, 4 folders (Box 65)
  - Educators for Bentley, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Offers of Assistance and Advice on Campaign (Box 65)
  - Campaign materials and expense sheets (Box 65)
  - Speeches, 5 folders (Box 65)
  - Reference and background materials, 4 folders (Box 65)
  - Bagwell, Paul, Committee (Box 65)
  - Other candidates, schedules, chairpeople, etc. (Box 65)
- Michigan Freedom from Hunger Council 1964-1965
  Michigan Freedom from Hunger Council (0.5 linear ft.; 1964-1965) includes correspondence, memoranda, minutes of the council, and other working papers.
  - General Information: constitution, proclamation, members, membership drive, etc. (Box 65)
  - Correspondence
    - November 1964-April 1965 (Box 65)
    - May-June 1965 (Box 65)
    - July-August 1965 (Box 65)
    - September 1965 (Box 65)
    - October 1965 (Box 65)
    - November 1965-March 1966 (Box 65)
  - Memoranda, Albert Applegate (Box 65)
  - Memoranda, Robert McComb (Box 65)
  - Minutes February-September 1965 (Box 65)
  - Press releases (Box 65)
  - Questionnaires for prospective members (Box 65)
  - Hillsdale, Michigan meeting (December 1964) (Box 65)
  - Finances (Box 65)
  - Michigan Project in Colombia, South America, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Notebooks, 2 folders (Box 65)
- Michigan-British Honduras (Belize) Partners of the Alliance 1966-1969
  Michigan-British Honduras (Belize) Partners of the Alliance (3.2 linear ft.; 1966-1969) consists of meeting files, files for individuals involved with the organization, financial and membership materials, and committee records.
  - National Association of the Partners of the Alliance, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Correspondence 1966-1969, 5 folders (Box 66)
  - Executive Committee (Box 66)
  - Committee Assignments (Box 66)
  - Organizational meeting June 20, 1966 (Box 66)
  - Meeting August 30, 1966 (Box 66)
  - Meeting October 25, 1966 (Box 66)
  - Meetings 1967 (Box 66)
  - Activity Status Report July 1967 (Box 66)
  - Rio de Janiero conference September 1967 (Box 66)
  - Meeting
    - April 25, 1968 (Box 66)
    - September 9, 1968 (Box 66)
    - October 18, 1968 (Box 66)
    - November 28, 1968 (Box 66)
  - Memoranda (Box 66)
  - Arnett, Jud (Box 66)
  - Eirman, Warren (Box 66)
  - Finegan, Betty, 3 folders (Box 66)